Memorabilia Collection, 1782-2011 (bulk 1866-1997): Finding Aid AC053
University Archives
- Series 10: Pins and Ribbons, 1895-2000; 8 boxes
  - Sesquicentennial ribbon, 1896; 1 item (Box 26)
    Black over orange, gold tassel; "Princeton Sesquicentennial Celebration 1896" in gold; "Class of '74" in black.
  - Sesquicentennial ribbon, 1896; 1 item (Box 26)
    Black over orange, gold tassel; "Princeton Sesquicentennial Celebration 1896" in gold; "Class of '88" in black.
  - Sesquicentennial ribbon, 1896; 1 item (Box 26)
    Black over orange, gold tassel; "Princeton Sesquicentennial Celebration 1896" in gold; "Class of '89" in black.
  - Sesquicentennial ribbon, 1896; 1 item (Box 26)
    Black over orange, gold tassel; "Princeton Sesquicentennial Celebration 1896" in gold; "Class of '94" in black.
  - Sesquicentennial ribbon, 1896; 1 item (Box 26)
    Black over orange, gold tassel; "Princeton Sesquicentennial Celebration 1896" in gold; "Class of 1900" in black.
  - Sesquicentennial ribbon, 1896; 1 item (Box 26)
    Orange, "'Let Us All Smile' '88 'Trojan.' Delegation to Princeton Sesquicentennial" in black.
  - Reunion pin, 1971; 1 item (Box 36)
    Class of 1936. 35th reunion.
    AR.2002.038
  - Reunion pin, 1936; 1 item (Box 36)
    Class of 1936
  - 25th reunion pin, 1936; 1 item (Box 36)
    Class of 1936. "Pride of Nassau" on front.
  - Reunion pin, undated; 1 item (Box 39)
    "Baker Combine" and a tiger on front.
    AR.2001.071
  - Reunion pin, undated; 1 item (Box 39)
    "Orbital Twist" and a flying tiger with years 45, 46, 48, 49, 50, 51 on front.
  - Reunion pin, undated; 1 item (Box 39)
    I love '48 reunion pin.
  - Reunion pin, 1963; 1 item (Box 39)
    Class of 1948. 15th reunion. "15th Anzac Patrol" on front.
  - Pin, 1998 Sept 19; 1 item (Box 39)
    Princeton University Stadium. September 19, 1998.
  - Reunion pin, 1973; 1 item (Box 39)
    Class of 1948. 25th reunion. Tiger smoking on front.
  - Reunion pin, 1998; 1 item (Box 39)
    Class of 1948. 50th reunion. Dancing Tiger.
  - Reunion pin, undated; 1 item (Box 39)
    Class of 1948. "ANZAC" on front.
  - Pin, 1996 Nov. 23; 1 item (Box 39)
    Farewell to Palmer pin.
  - 20th reunion pin, 1968; 1 item (Box 39)
    Class of 1948. Tiger with hat on front.
  - 45th reunion pin, 1993; 1 item (Box 39)
    Class of 1948. Tiger holding a flag and "It's Fabulous!" on the front.
  - 2001 reunions button, 1 item (Box 39)
    Tiger and "Princeton University".
    AR.2001.038
  - 1999 reunions button, 1 item (Box 39)
    Tiger on front.
    AR.2001.013
  - Pin, undated; 1 item (Box 39)
    WROC. "I support Princeton's workers."
    AR.2001.014
  - Reunion pin, 1990; 1 item (Box 39)
    Class of 1970. 20th reunion. Cicada and Princeton shield pattern.
  - Pin, 2000-12-13; 1 item (Box 39)
    Pin to commemorate the Centennial of the Graduate School. White with centennial logo and 100.
    AR.2000.143
  - Reunion pin, undated; 1 item (Box 39)
    Small Class of 1970 reunion pin.
  - Pin, 1996; 1 item (Box 39)
    Asian Pacific American Heritage Month. Princeton University 1996 pin.
    AR.2000.120
  - 20th reunion nametag pin, 1990; 1 item (Box 39)
    Princeton class of 1970.
  - 40th reunion nametag pin, 1988; 1 item (Box 39)
    Class of 1948. Tiger carrying a banner with blinking lights on it.
  - Pin, 1964; 1 item (Box 39)
    Alumni P-Rade 1964 pin.
  - Pin, 1958; 1 item (Box 39)
    Alumni P-Rade 1958 pin.
  - Pin, 1963; 1 item (Box 39)
    Alumni P-Rade 1963 pin.
  - Pin, 1962; 1 item (Box 39)
    Alumni P-Rade 1962 pin.
  - Pin, 1961; 1 item (Box 39)
    Alumni P-Rade 1961 pin.
  - 50th reunion pin, 1998; 1 item (Box 39)
    Class of 1948.
  - Reunion pin, 1936; 1 item (Box 39)
  - 60th reunion pin, 1936; 1 item (Box 39)
    Class of 1936.
  - Anniversary Campaign pin, undated; 1 item (Box 39)
    "Eventful" on the pin and three orange and black ribbons.
  - Pin, undated; 1 item (Box 39)
    The First 250.
  - Anniversary Campaign pin, undated; 1 item (Box 39)
    Black background with orange "ONE" on front.
  - Anniversary Campaign pin, undated; 1 item (Box 39)
    Orange background with black "ONE" on front
  - Anniversary Campaign pin, undated; 1 item (Box 39)
    "Eventful Staff".
  - Anniversary Campaign ribbon, undated; 1 item (Box 39)
    With One Accord.
  - Reunions button, undated; 1 item (Box 39)
    Class of 1952. Buster Brown on front.
    AR.2002.079
  - Reunions button, undated; 1 item (Box 39)
    Class of 1952. 52's Fission Frolic and Princeton shield on front.
  - Reunions button, undated; 1 item (Box 39)
    Princeton 1916, Doc Runk on front.
  - Pin, undated; 1 item (Box 39)
    Free Firestone by 500 pin.
    AR.2002.055
  - Reunions pin, undated; 1 item (Box 39)
    Class of 1970. Princeton cicada shield on front.
  - Misc. pins, undated; 1 item (Box 41)
    Miscellaneous pins (25) circa 1970s
  - Gold pins, undated; 1 item (Box 42)
    "The Old Guard of Nassau Hall" written around the outside with Princeton Shield in the middle.
  - Triangular pin, 1998-09-19; 1 item (Box 42)
  - Reunion pin, 1995; 1 item (Box 42)
    Small orange and black class of 1970 25th reunion pin with cicada shield.
    AR.2002.017
  - 10th Reunion pin, 1988; 1 item (Box 43)
    Tiger listening to record player and record with "78 RPM." "78 Turns 10. Reunion Party Machine."
    AR.2008.025
  - Reunion pin, undated; 1 item (Box 43)
    Tiger with tongue sticking out in a glass wearing wings and dunce cap. Camp fire, "Life".
  - 10th Reunion pin, 1990; 1 item (Box 43)
    Tiger with baseball bat. "80Bat," "Mye Lip."
  - Reunion pin, undated; 1 item (Box 43)
    Mottle design in brown and beige, "Hal Rogers."
  - 15th Reunion pin, 1991; 1 item (Box 43)
    Orange with tiger 15th Reunion pin. Orange with tiger arm holding bat, "15-All," "Princeton University," Fifteenth Reunion," "Class of 1976. "
  - 25th Reunion pin, 1993; 1 item (Box 43)
    Tiger wearing wizard cap, sitting on hourglass, "68's 25th," "I. Floyd."
  - Reunion pin, undated; 1 item (Box 43)
    Two dancing tigers, "73 revolution!," "Hal Morlan."
  - Pin, undated; 1 item (Box 43)
    Orange, "Free Firestone Library," "Open Access."
    AR.2008.057
  - Pin, undated; 1 item (Box 43)
    Orange, bold print "Free Firstone Library," "Open Access."
  - 10th Reunion pin, 1948; 1 item (Box 43)
    Orange with black trim and lettering. "1938," "Tenth," "Roger Clisham."
    AR.2008.080
  - Pin, 1953; 1 item (Box 43)
    Black with orange trim and lettering. "Alumni P-rade 1953."
  - Reunion pins, undated; 1 item (Box 44)
    2 miscellaneous reunion pins (circa 1925 and 1978)
  - 10th Reunion pin, 1979; 1 item (Box 44)
    Orange and round with Tiger pulling tiger by tail. "Going Back," " 69s 10th in 79," "June 7-9, 1979."
  - 15th Reunion pin, 1990; 1 item (Box 44)
    Black with white stripes, orange record in middle with "1990." "Sounds of '65."
  - 20th Reunion pin, 1989; 1 item (Box 44)
    White with jumping tiger and bird, orange sticker "Minor 1989." "69's Twentieth Reunion," "June 1-4, 1989," "Jenny Johnson," orange "1989."
  - 35th Reunion pin, 1991; 1 item (Box 44)
    White with Tiger on square cone. "The Great Class," "35th Reunion."
  - 35th Reunion pin, 1990; 1 item (Box 44)
    White with tiger sitting on planet earth, orange stripe and black letters, "'55/35th."
  - 35th Reunion pin, 1993; 1 item (Box 44)
    Orange with Princeton seal. "The Great class of 1958," "35th Reunion," "Christa Badger."
  - 20th Reunion pin, 1990; 1 item (Box 44)
    Orange with sombrero and mustache, white and organge sticker "Minor 1990." "Ole," "Anne Altmarier."
  - Reunion pin, undated; 1 item (Box 44)
    Orange and black with white and black stripe across middle. Large white "63."
  - Reunion pin, undated; 1 item (Box 44)
    White with leaning tiger, orange "64," "Richard Anderson."
  - Reunion pin, undated; 1 item (Box 44)
    White with open-mouthed tiger. "54," "Richard Anderson."
  - 5th Reunion pin, 1993; 1 item (Box 44)
    White with tiger in overalls, leaning on wooden "88on Tradition -- 1993."
  - 5th Reunion pin, 1990; 1 item (Box 44)
    White with tiger wearing sunglasses, playing piano. "1985's Cool Cats' 5th reunion."
    AR2008.025
  - 40th Reunion pin, 1989; 1 item (Box 44)
    White with Tiger face. "40th Reunion," "One for All - All Four Nine," "Brian Danella."
  - 42nd Reunion pin, 1993; 1 item (Box 44)
    White with orange border, tiger dressed as Revolution era solider, "1951's 42nd."
  - Reunion pin, undated; 1 item (Box 44)
    Orange with drawing of Cleveland Tower, "Graduate," "Alumni."
  - 25th Reunion pin, 1994; 1 item (Box 44)
    White with orange and black ying-yang, and dancing tigers. "The Spirit of '69," "25th Reunion," "Donald W. Altmaier."
  - Pin, 1990; 1 item (Box 44)
    White with tiger playing banjo. Red sticker with "1990," "1960-1990."
  - Pin, 1985; 1 item (Box 44)
    White with tiger shooting another tiger out of cannon. Orange "Thunderous 25th." "1960's."
  - Reunion pin, 1928; 1 item (Box 44)
    Orange background with black lettering. "'83," "18831988."
  - Ribbon, undated; 1 item (Box 44)
    Orange, tiger running in shorts. Black letters "Princeton Alumni Track Meet."
  - Pin, undated; 1 item (Box 44)
    Orange with black Princeton University emblem. "1938," "Roger Clisham."
  - Reunion pin, 1988; 1 item (Box 44)
    Orange with two tigers on eights. "38's Fiftieth, Original Combine '38, '39, '40, '41," "Roger Clisham."
  - Pin, undated; 1 item (Box 44)
    Black with wide orange stripe, black "Princeton" on orange.
  - Reunion pin, undated; 1 item (Box 44)
    Oval orange, with black Princeton Seal and Black letters "1938," "Reunion," "Pat Clisham."
  - Reunion pin, 1963; 1 item (Box 44)
    Orange with Princeton seal, black lettering "1938, 25th Reunion June 12-16 1963," "Roger Clisham."
  - 40th Reunion pin, 1978; 1 item (Box 44)
    Orange with Princeton seal, black lettering "1938," "40th Reunion," "June 1-4, 1978."
  - 45th Reunion pin, 1983; 1 item (Box 44)
    White, black and orange, with Princeton seal. "1938, 45th Reunion, June 2-4, 1983," "Roger Clisham."
  - Pins and Ribbons, undated; 1 item (Box 44)
    Miscellaneous pins and ribbons circa 1902-1940
  - Ribbon, 1957-06-15; 1 item (Box 75)
    Class of 1898. Orange ribbon with black button "Alumni P-rade 1957."
  - Ribbon, undated; 1 item (Box 75)
    Class of 1899. Orange ribbon with black lettering.
  - Ribbon, undated; 1 item (Box 75)
    AR.2005.087
  - Ribbon, undated; 1 item (Box 75)
  - Ribbon, undated; 1 item (Box 75)
    Class of 1899. Orange ribbon with black lettering. Still in plastic packaging.
  - Assorted ribbons, 1861-1898; 1 item (Box 47)
  - Assorted pins, 1940s-1990s; 1 item (Box 48)
    Miscellaneous pins (63), circa 1940s-1990s. These include pins commemorating Black History Month, 1993-1997; Native Americans at Princeton; Hispanic Heritage Month 1992 and Latino Heritage Month 1995-1996; Asian Pacific Heritage Month 1993 and 1995; a "PROUD" rainbow pin and a rainbow triangle pin "With liberty and justice for all."
  - Class of '45 fourth reunion pin, undated; 1 item (Box 178)
    Orange pin. Fourth reunion, '45. Joan.
    AC053.1732
  - Princeton Club of New York ribbon, 1896; 1 item (Box 178)
    Orange ribbon. The Princeton Club of New York. Sesqui-Centennial, October 22, 1896.
    AC053.1736
  - Pin and keychain, undated; 1 item (Box 143)
    Miscellaneous pin and keychain
- Series 11: Jewelry
  - Engagement ring, 1889; 1 item (Box 12)
    Ring, with monogram "PTS" encased. "My mother's engagement ring Julia D. Smith" (Caption on the original case).
    EX4471
  - Pendant for Knowlton '1900, circa 1900; 1 item (Box 12)
    Pendant. "I.O. of K. '99 to Jim Knowlton 1900"
    Given by Knowlton's grandson, Thomas W. Wright
  - Cuff links, undated; 1 item (Box 12)
    Cuff links with tiger and lion motif.
    62
  - Fencing pendant, circa 1924; 1 item (Box 12)
    Gold pendant with tiger. Front: "Princeton Intra Collegiate Athletic Association"; Back: "Fencing, 1924-25 EPEE."
    AR.2008.110
  - Phi Beta Kappa Fob, undated; 1 item (Box 45)
    Copper and with square centerpiece; engraved "S. Alexander December 05th 1776" on one side; Greek letters for Phi, Beta, Kappa engraved on the other.
    EX4304
  - Tiger claws set in gold and silver, circa 1912; 1 item (Box 45)
    2 tiger claws of different sizes; gold setting for the larger one, silver setting for the smaller one, both mounted with "94" and engraved "Society of the Claw Princeton University"; "Howard C. Butler Archaeologist" engraved on the larger claw.
    EX4245; H.C. Butler
  - Letter seal of John Maclean, undated; 1 item (Box 45)
    Carved agate stone [carnelian]. Letter seal of John Maclean (1816). "JM Ubi Libertas, Ibi Patria" engraved.
    EX4286; Gift of Henry E. Hale (1892), Sept. 19, 1935.
  - Tiger claw set in gold, circa 1912; 1 item (Box 45)
    Tiger claw, with gold setting engraved "Society of the Claw Princeton University" on one side, "Franklin S. Spalding Educator" on the other.
    EX4410
  - Sleeve link of coins, circa 1874; 1 item (Box 45)
    Sleeve link of coins. Unearthed near the Cannon.
    EX4796
  - Tie clip with seal, undated; 1 item (Box 45)
    Tie clip. With U seal.
  - Watch chain with seal, undated; 1 item (Box 45)
    Watch chain, with U seal.
  - Cuff links with seal, undated; 1 item (Box 45)
    Cuff links, with U seal.
  - Graduate council pendants, undated; 1 item (Box 45)
    Grad council pendants.
  - Class of 1925 pendant, undated; 1 item (Box 45)
    Pendant, "Princeton Pictorial", "KP Jr. '25" engraved on back.
    AR.1994.075
  - Class of 1935 cufflinks, undated; 1 item (Box 45)
    Cufflinks, painted with U. seal '35.
    AR.1996.062
  - Gold chain with pendants, undated; 1 item (Box 45)
    Gold chain with Princeton pendants.
  - Tiger Claw, circa 1912; 1 item (Box 45)
    "Society of the Claw, Princeton University" inscribed on cap.
  - Tiger Claws, circa 1912; 1 item (Box 45)
    "Society of the Claw, Princeton University, W.C. Spruance, Jr. no. 82" inscribed on metal cap.
  - Venable's silver button, 1782; 1 item (Box 106)
    Oval and engraved with "V 1782." Silver button worn by Richard N. Venable at his Princeton graduation in 1782.
    EX4295; Emma C. Venable
  - "91" buttons and charm, circa 1891; 1 item (Box 106)
    Buttons and charm. 3 buttons, all engraved with "'91" over orange and black background; a clapper engraved "91."
    EX4857; EX4858
  - "88" lapel buttons, circa 1888; 2 items (Box 106)
    Two '88 lapel buttons.
  - "92" lapel button, circa 1892; 1 item (Box 106)
    92 lapel button.
  - Class of 1926 lapel button, circa 1926; 1 item (Box 106)
    Lapel button. Class of 1926.
  - Class of 1936 lapel button, circa 1936; 1 item (Box 106)
    Lapel button. Class of 1936.
    EX4566
  - Class of 1941 lapel button, circa 1941; 1 item (Box 106)
    Lapel button. Class of 1941.
- Series 12: Athletic Equipment and Ephemera, 1876-1989; 12 boxes
  The series includes figurines, equipment, and clothing.
  - Baseball, 1876; 1 box (Box C.4)
    76 vs. 74, 76-7 74-4.
  - Basketball Tickets, 1966; 1 box (Box C.1)
    Feb 12, 1966. vs. Yale. About 50-60 tickets.
  - Cloth print, Undated; 1 box (Box C.1)
    Baseball player.
  - Cloth print, Undated; 1 box (Box C.1)
    Football player
  - Discus, 1896; 1 box (Box 27)
    AR.1996.086
    Robert Garrett 1897, threw this discus 95'7.5" and won first place at the first Olympic Games in modern times at Athens, Greece 1896. Note.0 It is unknown whether this discus or the unmounted one was the actual discus thrown. See Box C.02.
    Class of 1897
  - Discus, 1896; 1 box (Box C.2)
    Mounted Garrett discus used to win at the first Olympics of modern times at Athens, Greece. Note- it is unknown whether this discus or the mounted one was the actual discus thrown.
  - Figurine, Undated; 1 box (Box 40)
    Football player figurine. Black jersey with orange #6.
  - Figurine, Undated; 1 box (Box 40)
    AR.2010.037
    Football player holding ball and wearing a Princeton pin.
  - Football, 1951; 1 box (Box 19)
    AR.2005.049
    Princeton 12 - Brown 0. Signed by members of the 1951 team including Dick Kazmaier '52
  - Football jersey, Undated; 1 box (Box 7)
    Princeton football jersey. #70. Black with orange stripes and white numbers.
  - Football music player, Undated; 1 box (Box C.4)
    "Goin' Back"
  - Football Patch, 1989; 1 box (Box C.1)
    AR.1992.030
    "Princeton Tigers 1000 Nov 6, 1869 - Oct 21, 1989." About 50 Duplicates.
  - Framed invitation, Undated; 1 box (Box C.6)
    to a smoker at Princeton Inn, given by Pyne and Benson. (P-11, Yale-6)
  - Golf ball, 1955 June 10; 1 box (Box 11)
    Golf ball marked "I Beat Bill Campell."
    Given by Stanley W. Root, Jr. '45
  - Jewelry, 1922; 1 box (Box C.1)
    Gold Football watch fob. "R.W. Wingate Quarterback. 1922 Champions. P-3, Y-0. P-10, H3."
    Class of 1925
    letter enclosed. Given by Mrs. R.W. Wingate.
  - Megaphone, Undated; 1 box (Box C-Open (under stairs))
    Black with orange "P". Cheerleading.
  - Plate, 1973; 1 box (Box C.1)
    "Princeton-Yale Football Centennial" around edge, "1873-1973" and November 17, 1973 in center, with tiger, bulldog and football. Pewter.
  - Postcard, 1908; 1 box (Box C.1)
    June 6, 1908 Princeton-3 Yale-2. With tiger.
  - Tile, 1939; 1 box (Box C.1)
    1939. Princeton-20, Yale-7. "In the class' service"
    Class of 1939
  - Wooden Block, Undated; 1 box (Box C.1)
    with tiger and football helmet.
    Made for Austin P Leland, inherited by Donald Griffin
- Series 13: Stamps, Paper and Desk Accessories
  - 200th Anniversary stamp, 1956; 1 item (Box 80)
    200th Anniversary of Nassau Hall stamp. Glass container engraved on front "John T. Root '53."
  - 200th Anniversary stamp, 1956; 1 item (Box 106)
    200th Anniversary of Nassau Hall 1756-1956. $.03 US postage. In paperweight of Don Griff '23.
  - 200th Anniversary stamp, 1956; 1 item (Box 106)
    First day cover for Nassau Hall 200th Anniversary.
    AR.2000.117
  - 200th Anniversary stamp, 1956; 1 item (Box 106)
    $.03 postage; 200th anniversary of Nassau Hall.
  - Framed football player stamps and envelope, undated; 1 item (Box 173)
    White stamps with green picture of football player and coach. Red lettering "Football, 1869-1969."
    Separated from AC180. No prior provenance known.
  - Stamps, undated; 1 item (Box 21)
    Dry adhesive (stamps). Five different ones.
  - USS Princeton logos, undated; 1 item (Box 96)
    Stickers with logo of USS Princeton in envelope
  - USS Princeton pamphlet, undated; 1 item (Box 96)
    Pamphlet and memorandum describing the USS Princeton
  - Mousepad, undated; 1 item (Box 96)
    Circular mousepad. "Welcome Class of 2010."
  - Mousepad, undated; 1 item (Box 96)
    Circular mousepad. "Welcome Class of 2008."
  - Mousepad, undated; 1 item (Box 96)
    Circular mousepad. "Welcome Class of 2007."
  - Valentine card, undated; 1 item (Box 96)
    Valentine's greetings from Princeton University.
  - Woodrow Wilson card, undated; 1 item (Box 96)
    "Mr. Woodrow Wilson. Princeton, NJ"
    Given by R. Cullinane '70 on 7/2/73
  - 1906 Reunions cardboard panel, undated; 1 item (Box 96)
    Reunions. 1906. Bookmark?
  - Penn mascot decal, circa 1946; 1 item (Box 96)
    Penn mascot standing on tiger.
  - Class of 1970 locust magnet, 1995; 1 item (Box 96)
    White plastic square. "70's 25th" and image of locust and seal.
    AR.2000.019
  - Class of 1990 magnet, 1995; 1 item (Box 96)
    White rectangle. "Class of 1990's Fifth Reunion." Tiger in director's chair, calendar.
  - Princeton Inn notepad, undated; 1 item (Box 96)
    From the Princeton Inn (Forbes)
  - Packet of tiger stickers/patches, undated; 1 item (Box 96)
    Various tiger pictures. Exxon?
  - Mount Princeton postcard, undated; 1 item (Box 96)
    View of Mount Princeton, Colorado.
  - "Princeton Runabout" postcard, undated; 1 item (Box 96)
    "Princeton Runabout" Yellow car picture.
  - Class of 1909 tiger sticker for beer cans, undated; 1 item (Box 96)
    Reunions. Class of 1909
  - Class of 1919 tiger sticker for beer cans, undated; 1 item (Box 96)
    Reunions. Class of 1919
  - Princeton sticker, undated; 1 item (Box 96)
    Black P with orange background.
  - Wooden Block insignia stamp, undated; 1 item (Box 106)
    University insignia, books, diploma with Latin. 2".
  - Wooden Block tiger stamp, undated; 1 item (Box 106)
    Tiger with "P" on chest.
  - Paper weight, undated; 1 item (Box 20)
    Made for Robert A. Winters in machine shop in Palmer lab. Princeton shield with initials RAW on top.
    AR.2001.109
  - Pencil, undated; 1 item (Box 21)
    Orange and black striped pencil with tiger head.
  - Magnet, 1992; 1 item (Box 21)
    White plastc rectangle with dinosaur, number 10, and "Oldnassaurus."
  - Anniversary Campaign pen and pencil, undated; 1 item (Box 21)
    "With One Accord"
  - Book mark clip, undated; 1 item (Box 21)
    Gold P.
  - Pen, undated; 1 item (Box 21)
    The Pace Center for Community Service pen.
  - Plastic Cicada clip, undated; 1 item (Box 21)
    Class of 1970
  - Princeton Shield sticker, undated; 1 item (Box 21)
  - Stephen Alexander calling card plate, 1840-1880; 1 item (Box 106)
    Bronze and rectangular, "Prof. Stephen Alexander" engraved in mirror image.
    EX4794
  - Class of 1928 directory, 1972; 1 item (Box 106)
    Reunions. 1972 directory of class of 1928.
  - Class of 1927 55th reunion pen, 1982; 1 item (Box 106)
    Reunions. Class of 1927's 55th.
  - Paperweight portrait of Dr. McCosh, undated; 1 item (Box S-000007)
    Dr. McCosh. Paperweight.
  - Class of 1938 25th reunion coin collection can, 1963; 1 item (Box 109)
    Reunions. 1938's 25th in 1963. Orange.
  - Desk calendar, 1984; 1 item (Box 109)
    94 with plaster tiger.
  - Playing cards, undated; 1 item (Box 109)
    Dual pack. Princeton orange and black.
    Anonymous gift in memory of Charles W Millard, Jr. '26. 1989
  - Hibben inauguration paperweight(?), 1912; 1 item (Box 109)
    Glass with gold coin suspended in center, featuring bust of John Grier Hibben on one side, Nassau Hall on other. Commemorates Hibben's inauguration.
  - Inkwell and stand., 1963; 1 item (Box 112)
    Blown by Physics Glassblowers. Metal stand with "Princeton".
    Given 1972 with note.
  - Class of 1915 metal stamp, 1 item (Box 117)
    "Class of 1915"
  - Sophomore reception dance card, 1884 June 17; 1 item (Box 119)
    Covered with orange and black ribbon. "Princeton Sophomore Reception June 17, 1884."
  - George Shultz dollar bills, 1973; 1999; 1 item (Box 119)
    Two framed dollar bills signed by George P. Shultz '42, with letter from Shultz.
    AR.2000.029
  - Geology school cards in frame., 1928; 1 item (Box 119)
    Invite and expedition card to "Miss Miller for one night only"
    Gift of Frederick Redpath, given on Oct 6, 1994.
  - Postcard, undated; 1 item (Box 119)
    "Princeton" on banners. Framed.
  - Class of 1956 magnet, 2011; 1 item (Box 178)
    Class of 1956. 55th reunion. Small magnet.
    AR.2010.029
  - Sticker, undated; 1 item (Box 178)
    Orange paper with Princeton shield and "Princeton University" in black lettering. Adhesive worn off.
  - Meal ticket, 1967; 1 item (Box 21)
    Reunions. 1927's 40th.
  - Nassau Hall bookmark, undated; 1 item (Box 178)
    White bookmark with Princeton logo and image of Nassau Hall.
    AR2004.097
- Series 14: Smoking Accessories, 1870-1973; 18 boxes
  The series contains Princeton-themed tobacco smoking accessories, such as clay pipes from Class Day celebrations, lighters, ashtrays, cigarette packages, et cetera.
  - Class day clay pipe, 1877; 1 item (Box 31)
    1877 class day pipes.
    Given by Mrs. John Stewart, daughter of John Howell Weatcott '77, on March 25, 1963.
  - Clay pipe, 1938; 1 item (Box 73)
    1938 penciled on.
  - Class day clay pipe with ribbon, undated; 1 item (Box 73)